<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Research | Greenest A.I. Lab</title><link>https://greenest-ai.kangwon.ac.kr/tag/research.html</link><atom:link href="https://greenest-ai.kangwon.ac.kr/tag/research/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><description>Research</description><generator>Wowchemy (https://wowchemy.com)</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 01 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://greenest-ai.kangwon.ac.kr/media/logo.svg</url><title>Research</title><link>https://greenest-ai.kangwon.ac.kr/tag/research.html</link></image><item><title>National research project initiated</title><link>https://greenest-ai.kangwon.ac.kr/news/2025-09-011.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://greenest-ai.kangwon.ac.kr/news/2025-09-011.html</guid><description>&lt;p>Greenest A.I. has initiated a national research project titled ‘DWaRF-X,’ funded by the National Research Foundation (NRF). This ambitious project aims to develop advanced AI-driven solutions for dynamic water resource forecasting and management. By leveraging cutting-edge machine learning techniques and data analytics, DWaRF-X seeks to enhance the accuracy and efficiency of water resource predictions, ultimately contributing to sustainable water management practices. The project will involve collaboration with leading experts in hydrology, environmental science, and AI technology to address critical challenges in water resource planning and conservation. We are excited to embark on this innovative journey and look forward to the impactful outcomes that DWaRF-X will bring to the field of water resource management. Go DWARF!&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Research project initiated</title><link>https://greenest-ai.kangwon.ac.kr/news/2025-04-012.html</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://greenest-ai.kangwon.ac.kr/news/2025-04-012.html</guid><description>&lt;p>Greenest A.I. has initiated a research project titled ‘Mathematical optimization of decarbonization pathways,’ funded by the Chuncheon Carbon Neutrality Center. This project aims to develop advanced mathematical models and algorithms to optimize strategies for reducing carbon emissions across various sectors. By leveraging cutting-edge AI techniques, the research seeks to identify the most effective and efficient pathways to achieve carbon neutrality, contributing to global efforts in combating climate change. The project will involve collaboration with experts in environmental science, economics, and policy-making to ensure that the proposed solutions are both scientifically sound and practically implementable. We are excited to embark on this important initiative and look forward to making significant contributions to the field of sustainable development and environmental conservation.&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>