<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>News | Greenest A.I. Lab</title><link>https://greenest-ai.kangwon.ac.kr/news.html</link><atom:link href="https://greenest-ai.kangwon.ac.kr/news/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><description>News</description><generator>Wowchemy (https://wowchemy.com)</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 01 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://greenest-ai.kangwon.ac.kr/media/logo.svg</url><title>News</title><link>https://greenest-ai.kangwon.ac.kr/news.html</link></image><item><title>National research project initiated</title><link>https://greenest-ai.kangwon.ac.kr/news/2025-09-011.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://greenest-ai.kangwon.ac.kr/news/2025-09-011.html</guid><description>&lt;p>Greenest A.I. has initiated a national research project titled ‘DWaRF-X,’ funded by the National Research Foundation (NRF). This ambitious project aims to develop advanced AI-driven solutions for dynamic water resource forecasting and management. By leveraging cutting-edge machine learning techniques and data analytics, DWaRF-X seeks to enhance the accuracy and efficiency of water resource predictions, ultimately contributing to sustainable water management practices. The project will involve collaboration with leading experts in hydrology, environmental science, and AI technology to address critical challenges in water resource planning and conservation. We are excited to embark on this innovative journey and look forward to the impactful outcomes that DWaRF-X will bring to the field of water resource management. Go DWARF!&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Global collaboration meeting, NASA JPL</title><link>https://greenest-ai.kangwon.ac.kr/news/2025-07-151.html</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://greenest-ai.kangwon.ac.kr/news/2025-07-151.html</guid><description>&lt;p>Prof. SungKu Heo had a productive meeting with researchers from NASA&amp;rsquo;s Jet Propulsion Laboratory (JPL) to discuss potential global collaborations in the field of multi-scale modeling and monitoring of climate change adaptation. This collaboration aims to leverage advanced remote sensing technologies and data analytics to better understand and address the impacts of climate change on various ecosystems and communities. By combining expertise from both institutions, the partnership seeks to develop innovative solutions that can enhance climate resilience, improve resource management, and support sustainable development initiatives worldwide. The meeting marked the beginning of an exciting journey towards harnessing the power of multi-scale modeling to drive advancements in climate science and promote effective adaptation strategies. We look forward to the fruitful outcomes of this collaboration and the positive impact it will have on global efforts to combat climate change.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Invited lecture, Kyung Hee University</title><link>https://greenest-ai.kangwon.ac.kr/news/2025-06-021.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://greenest-ai.kangwon.ac.kr/news/2025-06-021.html</guid><description>&lt;p>Prof. SungKu Heo was invited to give a lecture on ‘Environmental issues on advanced technologies’ at Kyung Hee University. The lecture addressed the environmental challenges and considerations associated with the development and deployment of advanced technologies, including artificial intelligence, quantum computing, and other emerging innovations. The discussion highlighted the importance of sustainable practices in technology development to mitigate negative environmental impacts and promote eco-friendly advancements. The lecture also explored potential solutions and strategies for integrating environmental consciousness into technological progress, fostering a more sustainable future. Attendees gained valuable insights into the intersection of technology and environmental stewardship, emphasizing the need for collaborative efforts among researchers, industry professionals, and policymakers to address these critical issues. The event provided an excellent platform for knowledge exchange and inspired further dialogue on the role of advanced technologies in shaping a sustainable world.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Invited talk, NIER</title><link>https://greenest-ai.kangwon.ac.kr/news/2025-05-221.html</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://greenest-ai.kangwon.ac.kr/news/2025-05-221.html</guid><description>&lt;p>Prof. SungKu Heo was invited to present a talk titled ‘AI application into atmospheric environment’ at the National Institute of Environmental Research (NIER). The presentation focused on the innovative applications of artificial intelligence in monitoring and managing atmospheric conditions, emphasizing how AI can enhance environmental research and policy-making. The talk highlighted recent advancements in AI technologies and their potential to address challenges related to air quality, climate change, and environmental sustainability. The discussion also explored case studies and practical implementations of AI in atmospheric science, showcasing its ability to improve data analysis, predictive modeling, and decision-making processes. Attendees gained valuable insights into the transformative role of AI in environmental research and its implications for future developments in the field. The event provided an excellent platform for knowledge exchange and collaboration among researchers, policymakers, and industry professionals dedicated to advancing sustainable environmental solutions.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Welcome, Internship class of 2025</title><link>https://greenest-ai.kangwon.ac.kr/news/2025-05-131.html</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://greenest-ai.kangwon.ac.kr/news/2025-05-131.html</guid><description>&lt;p>We are excited to welcome our new interns, Joonhyung, Seungjoon, Kyungmin, and Sanggoo, to the Greenest A.I. Lab. These talented individuals will be focusing on multi-media environmental impact analyses, bringing fresh perspectives and innovative ideas to our research efforts. We are confident that their contributions will significantly enhance our mission to develop sustainable AI technologies. Please join us in welcoming them to the team and wishing them a successful internship experience!&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>New journal paper published (JCR 6.5%, IF: 6.7)</title><link>https://greenest-ai.kangwon.ac.kr/news/2025-05-011.html</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://greenest-ai.kangwon.ac.kr/news/2025-05-011.html</guid><description>&lt;p>Prof. SungKu Heo (Corresponding author) published a paper titled &amp;ldquo;Predictive monitoring of wastewater treatment performance using machine learning: A case study on a full-scale membrane bioreactor&amp;rdquo; in the Journal of Water Process Engineering (JCR 6.5%, IF: 6.7). This study explores the application of machine learning techniques to enhance the monitoring and performance prediction of wastewater treatment processes, specifically focusing on a full-scale membrane bioreactor system. The research highlights the potential of AI-driven approaches to improve operational efficiency, optimize treatment outcomes, and support sustainable water management practices. The findings contribute to the growing body of knowledge on the integration of advanced technologies in environmental engineering and water resource management. The paper is accessible via the following DOI link: &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1016/j.jwpe.2025.107718" target="_blank" rel="noopener">https://doi.org/10.1016/j.jwpe.2025.107718&lt;/a>.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Invited talk, Yonsei University</title><link>https://greenest-ai.kangwon.ac.kr/news/2025-04-161.html</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://greenest-ai.kangwon.ac.kr/news/2025-04-161.html</guid><description>&lt;p>Prof. SungKu Heo was invited to present a talk titled ‘Env AI: Green and digital new deal’ at Yonsei University. The presentation focused on the intersection of environmental sustainability and artificial intelligence, highlighting how AI technologies can drive green initiatives and support digital transformation in various industries. The talk emphasized the importance of integrating environmental considerations into AI development to foster a more sustainable future. The discussion also explored the potential of AI to address pressing environmental challenges, such as climate change, resource management, and pollution control. Attendees gained insights into the latest advancements in Env AI and its role in shaping a greener and more digitally connected world. The event provided an excellent platform for knowledge exchange and collaboration among academics, researchers, and industry professionals committed to advancing sustainable technologies.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Research project initiated</title><link>https://greenest-ai.kangwon.ac.kr/news/2025-04-012.html</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://greenest-ai.kangwon.ac.kr/news/2025-04-012.html</guid><description>&lt;p>Greenest A.I. has initiated a research project titled ‘Mathematical optimization of decarbonization pathways,’ funded by the Chuncheon Carbon Neutrality Center. This project aims to develop advanced mathematical models and algorithms to optimize strategies for reducing carbon emissions across various sectors. By leveraging cutting-edge AI techniques, the research seeks to identify the most effective and efficient pathways to achieve carbon neutrality, contributing to global efforts in combating climate change. The project will involve collaboration with experts in environmental science, economics, and policy-making to ensure that the proposed solutions are both scientifically sound and practically implementable. We are excited to embark on this important initiative and look forward to making significant contributions to the field of sustainable development and environmental conservation.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Welcome, Seonju</title><link>https://greenest-ai.kangwon.ac.kr/news/2025-04-011.html</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://greenest-ai.kangwon.ac.kr/news/2025-04-011.html</guid><description>&lt;p>We are thrilled to welcome Sunjoo to the Greenest A.I. Lab as an integrated BS/MS student. Sunjoo embarks on an exciting journey focused on AI-driven autonomous design and process intensification. Her passion and dedication to advancing sustainable technologies make her a valuable addition to our team. Join us in wishing Sunjoo great success in her endeavors at the lab! Go Sunjoo!&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Global collaboration meeting, Imperial College London</title><link>https://greenest-ai.kangwon.ac.kr/news/2025-03-311.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://greenest-ai.kangwon.ac.kr/news/2025-03-311.html</guid><description>&lt;p>Prof. SungKu Heo had a productive meeting with researchers from Imperial College London to discuss potential global collaborations in the field of quantum machine learning applied to the water sector. This collaboration aims to leverage cutting-edge quantum computing techniques to address critical challenges in water management and sustainability. By combining expertise from both institutions, the partnership seeks to develop innovative solutions that can enhance water quality monitoring, optimize resource allocation, and improve overall water system efficiency. The meeting marked the beginning of an exciting journey towards harnessing the power of quantum machine learning to drive advancements in environmental technology and promote sustainable water practices worldwide. We look forward to the fruitful outcomes of this collaboration and the positive impact it will have on the global water sector.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Welcome, Founding Interns</title><link>https://greenest-ai.kangwon.ac.kr/news/2025-03-101.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://greenest-ai.kangwon.ac.kr/news/2025-03-101.html</guid><description>&lt;p>We are excited to welcome our founding interns, Jeongun, Wonjae, and Taeyoun, to the Greenest A.I. Lab. These talented individuals bring a wealth of knowledge and enthusiasm to our team, and we are thrilled to have them on board as we embark on our mission to develop sustainable AI technologies. They will be focusing their research on Multimodal AI, exploring innovative ways to integrate and analyze data from multiple sources to enhance the capabilities and applications of artificial intelligence in addressing environmental challenges. Please join us in welcoming them to the team and wishing them a successful internship experience!&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Hello World!</title><link>https://greenest-ai.kangwon.ac.kr/news/2025-03-011.html</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://greenest-ai.kangwon.ac.kr/news/2025-03-011.html</guid><description>&lt;p>The Greenest A.I. Lab has officially launched at Kangwon National University, marking a significant step towards achieving climate neutrality in the field of artificial intelligence. This state-of-the-art facility is dedicated to researching and developing sustainable AI technologies that minimize environmental impact while maximizing efficiency and performance.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title/><link>https://greenest-ai.kangwon.ac.kr/news/2025-10-131.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://greenest-ai.kangwon.ac.kr/news/2025-10-131.html</guid><description/></item></channel></rss>