<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Activity | Greenest A.I. Lab</title><link>https://greenest-ai.kangwon.ac.kr/tag/activity.html</link><atom:link href="https://greenest-ai.kangwon.ac.kr/tag/activity/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><description>Activity</description><generator>Wowchemy (https://wowchemy.com)</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://greenest-ai.kangwon.ac.kr/media/logo.svg</url><title>Activity</title><link>https://greenest-ai.kangwon.ac.kr/tag/activity.html</link></image><item><title>Greenest A.I participates KSEE</title><link>https://greenest-ai.kangwon.ac.kr/news/2025-11-201.html</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://greenest-ai.kangwon.ac.kr/news/2025-11-201.html</guid><description>&lt;p>We participated in the conference of the Korean Society of Environmental Engineers (KSEE) held on November 20 at Shinhwa World, Jeju Island.
Prof. SungKu Heo and undergraduate student Seonju Kim attended the conference to share and discuss recent research activities related to data-driven and AI-based approaches for environmental engineering systems. Go Greenest!&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Poster Presentation on Water AI-Based N₂O Soft-Sensing</title><link>https://greenest-ai.kangwon.ac.kr/news/2025-11-072.html</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://greenest-ai.kangwon.ac.kr/news/2025-11-072.html</guid><description>&lt;p>Seonju Kim, an integrated BS/MS course student, presented a poster at the 2025 Fall Meeting of the Korean Society of Industrial and Engineering Chemistry (KSIEC), held on November 7, 2025, at EXCO, Daegu.
The poster presentation was titled “Development of an N₂O Soft-Sensing Algorithm Based on Water AI-Ready Data,” and focused on the development of a data-driven soft-sensing framework for N₂O emissions using water AI-ready datasets.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Our Lab's Founding team recives encouragement prize in KOSAE</title><link>https://greenest-ai.kangwon.ac.kr/news/2025-10-161.html</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://greenest-ai.kangwon.ac.kr/news/2025-10-161.html</guid><description>&lt;p>The founding team delivered the first presentation of our lab in KOSAE, and we are thrilled to share that we received the &lt;a href="https://drive.google.com/file/d/122voRNTE8TtOIwGI49BZHYPaxPShTLlA/view?usp=drive_link" target="_blank" rel="noopener">encouragement prize&lt;/a> for our work. Our team developed an innovative forecasting model called M3-PMFormer, which predicts particulate matter (PM2.5 and PM10) across South Korea in both spatial and temporal domains. This AI system effectively captures the complex spatio-temporal dynamics of PM concentrations using a multimodal dataset. Go three idiots!!&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>We provide the first conference presentation</title><link>https://greenest-ai.kangwon.ac.kr/news/2025-10-152.html</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://greenest-ai.kangwon.ac.kr/news/2025-10-152.html</guid><description>&lt;p>The founding team (Taeyoon, Jeongun, Wonjae) provide the first conference presentation of our lab in KOSAE. We developed a forecasting model framework called M3-PMFormer to forecast particulate matter (PM) 2.5, and 10 spatially and temporally across South Korea. This novel AI framework can figure out spatio-temporal dynamics of PM2.5 and PM10 from the multimodality dataset. Go three idiots !!&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Panel Discussion on Net-Zero Water Management at CGWF 2025</title><link>https://greenest-ai.kangwon.ac.kr/news/2025-09-251.html</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://greenest-ai.kangwon.ac.kr/news/2025-09-251.html</guid><description>&lt;p>Prof. SungKu Heo participated in a panel discussion during Session 1: “New Challenges in Water Management Toward Net Zero” at the Chuncheon Global Water Forum 2025, where he shared perspectives based on his work in environmental systems and water and wastewater process modeling and optimization.
In the discussion, Prof. Heo emphasized that achieving net-zero water management requires a structured evaluation of carbon emissions across multiple scopes. He highlighted the importance of assessing direct emissions from water and wastewater treatment processes (Scope 1), energy-related emissions associated with electricity and energy use (Scope 2), and indirect emissions arising from supply chains and related activities (Scope 3). He further noted that recent discussions have expanded to Scope 4, which considers avoided or reduced emissions enabled by improved technologies and systems.
He also introduced data-driven and artificial intelligence–based operational optimization as a practical pathway for reducing emissions, noting that improvements in operational efficiency can significantly reduce energy-related emissions in treatment facilities.
In addition, Prof. Heo discussed the role of nature-based solutions (Nbs), emphasizing that clear and explicit design is required to determine which NBS technologies should be selected and implemented, as their effectiveness depends on defined objectives, site-specific conditions, and robust evaluation frameworks.
The session facilitated in-depth discussions among experts from academia, industry, and policy sectors, providing a meaningful platform for exploring strategies toward carbon-neutral and sustainable water management.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>An oral presentation was delivered at the 2025 Fall Meeting of KSIEC.</title><link>https://greenest-ai.kangwon.ac.kr/news/2025-11-071.html</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://greenest-ai.kangwon.ac.kr/news/2025-11-071.html</guid><description>&lt;p>A presentation was delivered at the 2025 Fall Meeting and Conference of the Korean Society of Environmental Engineers (KSIEC), held on November 7, 2025, at EXCO, Daegu.
Prof. SungKu Heo presented “Towards Circular Water Economy: Process Systems Engineering Applications in the Wastewater Sector” in Session 2LB-5. The presentation focused on the application of process systems engineering to water and wastewater treatment processes, with emphasis on process modeling and system-level optimization to support a circular water economy.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Greenest A.I. participates KOSAE</title><link>https://greenest-ai.kangwon.ac.kr/news/2025-10-151.html</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://greenest-ai.kangwon.ac.kr/news/2025-10-151.html</guid><description>&lt;p>We participate conference of KOSAE(Korean Society for Atmospheric Environment) to provide our recent research on 1) Nationwide spatio-temporal forecasting of particulate matter using Multimodal AI and 2) data-centric softsensor AI for trace air pollutants. Go Greenest!&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Global collaboration meeting, NASA JPL</title><link>https://greenest-ai.kangwon.ac.kr/news/2025-07-151.html</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://greenest-ai.kangwon.ac.kr/news/2025-07-151.html</guid><description>&lt;p>Prof. SungKu Heo had a productive meeting with researchers from NASA&amp;rsquo;s Jet Propulsion Laboratory (JPL) to discuss potential global collaborations in the field of multi-scale modeling and monitoring of climate change adaptation. This collaboration aims to leverage advanced remote sensing technologies and data analytics to better understand and address the impacts of climate change on various ecosystems and communities. By combining expertise from both institutions, the partnership seeks to develop innovative solutions that can enhance climate resilience, improve resource management, and support sustainable development initiatives worldwide. The meeting marked the beginning of an exciting journey towards harnessing the power of multi-scale modeling to drive advancements in climate science and promote effective adaptation strategies. We look forward to the fruitful outcomes of this collaboration and the positive impact it will have on global efforts to combat climate change.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Invited lecture, Kyung Hee University</title><link>https://greenest-ai.kangwon.ac.kr/news/2025-06-021.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://greenest-ai.kangwon.ac.kr/news/2025-06-021.html</guid><description>&lt;p>Prof. SungKu Heo was invited to give a lecture on ‘Environmental issues on advanced technologies’ at Kyung Hee University. The lecture addressed the environmental challenges and considerations associated with the development and deployment of advanced technologies, including artificial intelligence, quantum computing, and other emerging innovations. The discussion highlighted the importance of sustainable practices in technology development to mitigate negative environmental impacts and promote eco-friendly advancements. The lecture also explored potential solutions and strategies for integrating environmental consciousness into technological progress, fostering a more sustainable future. Attendees gained valuable insights into the intersection of technology and environmental stewardship, emphasizing the need for collaborative efforts among researchers, industry professionals, and policymakers to address these critical issues. The event provided an excellent platform for knowledge exchange and inspired further dialogue on the role of advanced technologies in shaping a sustainable world.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Invited talk, NIER</title><link>https://greenest-ai.kangwon.ac.kr/news/2025-05-221.html</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://greenest-ai.kangwon.ac.kr/news/2025-05-221.html</guid><description>&lt;p>Prof. SungKu Heo was invited to present a talk titled ‘AI application into atmospheric environment’ at the National Institute of Environmental Research (NIER). The presentation focused on the innovative applications of artificial intelligence in monitoring and managing atmospheric conditions, emphasizing how AI can enhance environmental research and policy-making. The talk highlighted recent advancements in AI technologies and their potential to address challenges related to air quality, climate change, and environmental sustainability. The discussion also explored case studies and practical implementations of AI in atmospheric science, showcasing its ability to improve data analysis, predictive modeling, and decision-making processes. Attendees gained valuable insights into the transformative role of AI in environmental research and its implications for future developments in the field. The event provided an excellent platform for knowledge exchange and collaboration among researchers, policymakers, and industry professionals dedicated to advancing sustainable environmental solutions.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Global collaboration meeting, Imperial College London</title><link>https://greenest-ai.kangwon.ac.kr/news/2025-03-311.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://greenest-ai.kangwon.ac.kr/news/2025-03-311.html</guid><description>&lt;p>Prof. SungKu Heo had a productive meeting with researchers from Imperial College London to discuss potential global collaborations in the field of quantum machine learning applied to the water sector. This collaboration aims to leverage cutting-edge quantum computing techniques to address critical challenges in water management and sustainability. By combining expertise from both institutions, the partnership seeks to develop innovative solutions that can enhance water quality monitoring, optimize resource allocation, and improve overall water system efficiency. The meeting marked the beginning of an exciting journey towards harnessing the power of quantum machine learning to drive advancements in environmental technology and promote sustainable water practices worldwide. We look forward to the fruitful outcomes of this collaboration and the positive impact it will have on the global water sector.&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>