<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Team | Greenest A.I. Lab</title><link>https://simongravelle.github.io/tag/team.html</link><atom:link href="https://simongravelle.github.io/tag/team/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><description>Team</description><generator>Wowchemy (https://wowchemy.com)</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://simongravelle.github.io/media/logo.svg</url><title>Team</title><link>https://simongravelle.github.io/tag/team.html</link></image><item><title>Welcome, Internship class of 2025</title><link>https://simongravelle.github.io/news/2025-05-131.html</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://simongravelle.github.io/news/2025-05-131.html</guid><description>&lt;p>We are excited to welcome our new interns, Joonhyung, Seungjoon, Kyungmin, and Sanggoo, to the Greenest A.I. Lab. These talented individuals will be focusing on multi-media environmental impact analyses, bringing fresh perspectives and innovative ideas to our research efforts. We are confident that their contributions will significantly enhance our mission to develop sustainable AI technologies. Please join us in welcoming them to the team and wishing them a successful internship experience!&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Welcome, Sunjoo</title><link>https://simongravelle.github.io/news/2025-04-011.html</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://simongravelle.github.io/news/2025-04-011.html</guid><description>&lt;p>We are thrilled to welcome Sunjoo to the Greenest A.I. Lab as an integrated BS/MS student. Sunjoo embarks on an exciting journey focused on AI-driven autonomous design and process intensification. Her passion and dedication to advancing sustainable technologies make her a valuable addition to our team. Join us in wishing Sunjoo great success in her endeavors at the lab! Go Sunjoo!&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Welcome, Founding Interns</title><link>https://simongravelle.github.io/news/2025-03-101.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://simongravelle.github.io/news/2025-03-101.html</guid><description>&lt;p>We are excited to welcome our founding interns, Jeongun, Wonjae, and Taeyoun, to the Greenest A.I. Lab. These talented individuals bring a wealth of knowledge and enthusiasm to our team, and we are thrilled to have them on board as we embark on our mission to develop sustainable AI technologies. They will be focusing their research on Multimodal AI, exploring innovative ways to integrate and analyze data from multiple sources to enhance the capabilities and applications of artificial intelligence in addressing environmental challenges. Please join us in welcoming them to the team and wishing them a successful internship experience!&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>